Inkyu Shin | Curriculum Vitae

☑ dlsrbgg33@kaist.ac.kr

I am a second-year Ph.D. student at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) under the co-supervision of Prof. Kuk-Jin Yoon and Prof. In So Kweon. I earned my B.S and M.S degrees in automotive engineering from Hanyang University(HYU) and KAIST in 2019 and 2021. I was a research intern at NEC Laboratories America, Inc, San Jose, CA (virtual).

Research Interests

My research interests currently lie in computer vision. Specifically, I pursue the goal of effectively processing data and building strong recognition model in computer vision. Followings are my main research topics.

- Semantic Segmentation
- Domain Adaptation and Generalization
- Simulated Learning
- Self-supervised Learning

Ultimately, the purpose of these researches is to apply to a variety of applications (e.g., Autonomous driving, Robot Navigation, AR/VR).

Research Experience

NEC Laboratoria America Inc

| | NEC Laboratories America, Inc | San Jose, CA (virtual) |
|--|---|------------------------|
| | Research Intern, Supervisor: Yi-Hsuan Tsai. | May 2021 - Aug 2021 |
| | Korea University | Seoul, Korea |
| | Research Intern, Supervisor: Jaegul Choo. | Sep 2018 - Dec 2018 |
| | Hanyang University | Seoul, Korea |

Research Assistant, Supervisor: Myuong-Ho Sunwoo

Samsung Electronics
Intern, Semi-conductor Test Group.

Jul 2018 - Aug 2018 **Hwasung, Korea** Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING Ph.D. degree, Advisor: In So Kweon

2021–

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING M.S degree, Advisor: In So Kweon

Master's Thesis: Learning to Scale the Labels for Self-training based Domain Adaptation

Hanyang University (HYU)

Output

AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERING B.S degree

Seoul, Korea
2013–2019

Publications

(C: conference / J: journal / P: preprint / * :equal contributions)

International Conference.....

- [P1] Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Video Semantic Segmentation Kwanyong Park*, Inkyu Shin*, Sanghyun Woo, In So Kweon arXiv, 2021
- [C5] LabOR: Labeling Only if Required for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Inkyu Shin, Dong-Jin Kim, Jae Won Cho, Sanghyun Woo, Kwanyong Park, In So Kweon International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021 (Oral)
 - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- [C4] Discover, Hallucinate, and Adapt:
 Open Compound Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation
 Kwanyong Park, Sanghyun Woo, Inkyu Shin, In So Kweon
 Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2020
 - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2021.
- o [C3] Two-phase Pseudo Label Densification for Self-training based Domain Adaptation Inkyu Shin, Sanghyun Woo, Fei pan, In So Kweon European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020
 - Also presented at "Visual Learning with Limited Labels" Workshops in conjunction with (CVPR), 2020
- [C2] Unsupervised Intra-domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation through Self-Supervision
 Fei pan, Inkyu Shin, Francois Rameau, Seokju Lee, In So Kweon
 Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020 (Oral)
 - Received Qualcomm Innovation Award 2020.
- [C1] Image-to-Image Translation via Group-wise Deep Whitening-and-Coloring Transformation Wonwoong Cho, Sungha Choi, David Keetae Park, Inkyu Shin, Jaegul Choo Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2019 (Oral)

IT skills

- Languages: Python, MATLAB, C, LATEX
- Libraries: PyTorch

References

- In So Kweon, Professor, KAIST iskweon@kaist.ac.kr
- Kuk-Jin Yoon, Professor, KAIST kjyoon@kaist.ac.kr

Service

o Military Service: Graduated from US Army Sergeant school(WLC) as KATUSA.